First of all I would like to come to you ma'am
what is in the list today
ma'am your mic is muted kindly unmuted
yes see the budget is also coming and I have been bullish on this
sector for a long time, so for
both these reasons I
feel that the insurance sector can
perform well in the coming time,
if I am specific in the insurance sector then
my pick today will be
of ICCI Jais, ASI Lord
Insurance
is currently trading
at 1432, my target for this for the coming month and a half will be
and we can keep a small stop loss on this,
target of 1500 and stop loss of 08 we can keep this
because I am so
bullish on this stock, of course with the
current market situation we have
kept a little squeeze in target for it,
we have not kept a big target for it, that is
why I am so much interested
in this stock or this sector
If you look at the price-to-earnings ratio, no matter
how bullish it is or how much it has
risen in the recent past,
its price-to-earnings
ratio is still quite low compared to the industry average. The
industry average for this
sector is around 42 times. The
price-to-earnings ratio of ICC GI is
still trading at 39.
Its earnings have been growing at a
CAGR of around 10 to 15 percent in the
past five years,
and I am talking about it growing in the
same manner in the times to come. The
second factor that
attracts me a lot about ICICI GA is the
consistent inflow of big data. In terms of big
data, FIIs, DIIs, or
mutual funds have been very
interested in
this particular stock in the last quarter,
and it is expected that
their interest in this particular stock will continue in the coming quarters as well.
These are some of the
fundamental factors.  It
's a fantastic stock. Fundamentally, there's no problem with it.
Revenue-wise, it's 17.8%. Revenue-
wise, you've seen profits in it. Its revenue percentage has been good for the past
few times.
Net profit is also quite
good, and similarly, your
operating profit is also quite good in this particular stock. So, all in all, no
matter how the market is, because of the budget
or let's say because of its past performance
fundamentals, this stock has
full chances of performing well.
Yes, okay, so the first ratio has come,
yes ma'am, yes, yes, one of
my bearish stocks
is also ABFRL. You can trade in futures in it.
If you are a risky trader, then the current
trade of ABFRL is right now. The
current price of ABFRL stock is currently
trading at 21.7. You
can take a position in it. This stock of yours has
come up after making today's low, so
you can go a little higher, you can let it go.
You can adopt Selen Rai for a particular stock,
you can also take a position on the price, there
is no problem in that, so
you can keep its target at 21.7 p.
Its target is 217, 217
is short term, you can trade it for two-three days,
you can set a target of 217 in it
and your
stop loss in this will be 225, so it is a
short term trade, ABF RL, its
analysis, its back bias, is
fundamental, it is above the technical, it is
absolutely above the technical, it has
made a high and has consistently
come in a bearish zone, it has been falling consistently
for the last few days
and it is quite good, its option is
also indicating bearish mode
in it very well, so these two stocks will be
my picks today, yes,
okay, two stocks have come from Madhu Ma'am,
Ma'am told me such general
insurance and also  Along with Aditya Birla
Fashion, the targets of both have been mentioned, one on the bearish side and the other on the long side, the
time
frame has been mentioned, you
can add this to your portfolio if you want,
okay Alok Sir